i spring pens welcome to another
我春天笔欢迎到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装弹簧提示
installment we're gonna look at
我们要看的分期付款
Microsoft Azur and the integration that
Microsoft Azur及其集成
they have built in corporation with the
他们已经与
spring team to support the use of that
春季队支持使用
platform okay now I'm a big believer
平台好了，现在我是一个大信徒
that of course you shouldn't you should
那你当然不应该
whenever possible take full advantage of
尽可能利用
the platform on which you're already
您已经在其上的平台
where you'll find compelling
在这里你会发现引人注目的
differentiating services and Microsoft
区分服务和Microsoft
Azure is chock-full of them naturally
Azure很自然地充满了他们
I'm always of the sort of position that
我一直是这样的职位
you shouldn't couple yourself to a
你不应该将自己耦合到一个
particular platform unnecessarily of
不必要的特定平台
course so it's for this reason that
当然是因为这个原因
Microsoft's nominated pivotal over many
微软的提名举足轻重
years to be the to be their sort of
年成为他们的那种
number one partner right we're a good
排名第一的合作伙伴，我们是一个好人
partner because we do have app instance
合作伙伴，因为我们确实有应用程序实例
consumption on their platform people use
人们在其平台上消费
Cloud Foundry pivotal Cloud Foundry on
Cloud Foundry关键的Cloud Foundry
top of Microsoft Azure and this is a
Microsoft Azure的顶部，这是一个
very natural pattern and a very natural
非常自然的图案和非常自然的
sort of a arrangement people use
人们使用的一种安排
Microsoft services infrastructure things
微软服务基础设施
like that that are managed by Microsoft
像这样，由Microsoft管理
that provide value to applications that
为应用程序提供价值
are differentiating things on that
在这方面与众不同
platform and then they where necessary
平台，然后在必要时
use those but they also don't couple
用那些，但他们也不会
themselves to that particular platform
自己到那个特定平台
just because they don't need to right
只是因为他们不需要纠正
there's no there's no reason in this day
这一天没有任何理由
and age to a couple yourself for things
和年龄一对夫妇自己的事情
like running a job our node application
就像在作业中运行我们的节点应用程序一样
right so you can use Cloud Foundry or
正确，因此您可以使用Cloud Foundry或
you know at the worst you could use
你知道在最坏的情况下你可以使用
something like kubernetes but either way
像kubernetes之类的东西
you have this sort of bit of indirection
你有这种间接
between your application and the
在您的应用程序和
underlying platform so what I want to
基础平台，所以我想要
talk to you today about is how to use
今天和您谈谈如何使用
spring cloud and spring boot along with
春天的云和春天的靴子以及
Microsoft Azure
微软Azure
the integration for Microsoft Azure and
Microsoft Azure和
that development that integration is
整合就是这样的发展
something that I regard with the
我认为与
optimism and enthusiasm because I've
乐观和热情，因为我
been privy to its development I've
我一直不知道它的发展
watched it grow from all but all of
看着它从几乎所有的事物中成长
nothing from a couple years ago to this
从几年前到现在都没有
really compelling sort of integration
真正引人注目的整合
that you know reasonably full-featured
您知道功能齐全
it grows pretty quickly the teams are
团队成长很快
the teams that develop it I've worked
我工作过的开发团队
with I've had the privilege of working
我有幸工作
with the teams that work on it in both
与两个团队一起工作
Redmond where of course Microsoft is
雷德蒙德微软当然在哪里
headquartered and in Shanghai China so
总部位于中国上海
it's just nice to see this this
看到这个很高兴
intubation grow so compellingly so so
气管插管如此引人注目
usefully in just such a short period of
在这么短的时间内有用
time so today we're going to build a
时间，所以今天我们要建立一个
very simple application we're gonna call
我们将调用非常简单的应用程序
this bootiful sewer and when use D Azur
这个下流的下水道，使用D Azur时
support I'm gonna use Azure storage but
支持我将使用Azure存储，但
really there's a bunch of other starters
真的还有很多其他的启动器
that we're gonna add along the way but
我们将一路添加，但
really the only one we need is support
真的，我们唯一需要的就是支持
I'm just adding storage because that's
我只是添加存储空间，因为那是
just one less thing for me to add in
我只需少添加一点
manually later on we're also gonna use
稍后再手动使用
the web support the Lombok support we're
网络支持我们提供的Lombok支持
gonna use a sequel server right that's
要使用续集服务器
actually not even part of the
实际上甚至不属于
integration with Microsoft's you know
与Microsoft的整合您知道
that's not that's not part of the spring
那不是春天的一部分
integration from Microsoft that's just a
来自Microsoft的集成只是一个
thing that spring boot does for you
春季靴帮你做的事情
today you know there's nothing
今天你知道什么都没有
particular about that you just add
关于您刚刚添加的内容
sequel server just like you would my
续集服务器就像你会
sequel or Postgres or h2 or any other
续集或Postgres或h2或任何其他
sort of stock standard a sequel driver
某种股票标准的续集推动者
so we're gonna add a sequel server we're
所以我们要添加一个续集服务器
gonna add actuator that's nice at weight
要增加重量轻的执行器
you know I'm not even sure there's a
你知道我什至不确定
particular reason to use it here it's
在这里使用它的特殊原因是
just nice to have that it's always good
拥有它总是很好真是太好了
to have that and I think that's it
有那个，我想就是这样
that's it for now so we're gonna go
现在就这样，我们要走了
ahead and generate a new project I'm
并生成一个新项目
using spring boot to Dino six and and
使用 spring boot 到恐龙六和
that'll be that'll be it okay so we'll
那样就可以了，所以我们会
hit generate and I'm going to open this
打generate，我要打开它
project up in our IDE as usual so here
像往常一样在我们的IDE中进行投影，所以这里
we are
我们是
CD downloads Azur o palm there XML
CD下载Azur o palm there XML
now we're gonna be using Microsoft Azure
现在我们将要使用Microsoft Azure
Microsoft Azure you you can get it's
Microsoft Azure您可以得到它
pretty trivial to get a free account you
获得免费帐户非常简单
can set up and they even have like a you
可以成立，他们甚至像你
know have a free trial that gives you
知道有免费试用版可以给你
some free credits and all that kind of
一些免费积分和所有这类
stuff I'm not sure the specifics but I
我不确定具体细节，但我
haven't count as well and I'm already
还不算数，我已经
logged in so I'm gonna go to the portal
登录，所以我要去门户
to my account rather to portal coming
到我的帐户，而不是门户网站
here we are I mean you get when you dump
在这里，我们是指您在转储时得到
when you get dumped into the portal
当您进入门户网站时
you're confronted with all these sort of
你面临着所有这些
amazing things that you've got there
你在那里的神奇事物
I've got some favorites in my dashboard
我的仪表板上有一些收藏夹
here but you can see that if I go to
在这里，但是你可以看到，如果我去
create a resource there is a whole
创建资源有一个整体
galaxy of things I can I can play with
我可以玩的东西的银河系
here right there's some blockchain and
这里有一些区块链，
identity management and security and
身份管理与安全
different kinds of messaging
不同种类的消息传递
technologies for IOT versus
物联网技术与
transactional versus messaging you know
您知道的事务性与消息传递
inventing and storage options and AI and
发明和存储选项以及AI和
machine learning and all that's really
机器学习以及所有这些
kind of interesting stuff compute
一种有趣的东西计算
primitives I wouldn't necessarily use
我不一定要使用的原语
any of these actually these are I think
这些中的任何一个我都认为
a little level make they're sort of they
一点点的水平使他们有点像
missed the point which is that you
错过了你的要点
shouldn't need to use these things to
不需要使用这些东西来
copy yourself to the platform use
复制自己到平台使用
something like Bundy but you know good
像邦迪这样的东西，但你知道很好
stuff like that right lots of
诸如此类的东西
interesting stuff here you know there's
有趣的东西在这里，你知道那里
even tutorials you can follow so that's
甚至是您可以遵循的教程，
nice I mean it's just really really
很好，我的意思是真的
compelling I've got a few things already
令人信服的我已经有几件事
provisioned in my account here I can see
在这里我的帐户中配置了我可以看到
the resources that I've got I can see
我可以看到的资源
all that kind of stuff if I go to my
所有这些东西，如果我去我的
dashboard oops dashboard oh actually
仪表盘哦，仪表盘哦，实际上
that was pretty kind of an instant view
那真是一个即时视图
looking at all services shows you a sort
查看所有服务会发现您有点
of an expanded view of all the things
所有事物的扩展视图
that are available to you and I think
可供您使用，我认为
that's really compelling I mean you can
这真的很引人注目，我的意思是你可以
see here for example you've got cosmos
例如在这里看到你有宇宙
TV you've got sequel server you've got
拥有续集服务器的电视
Redis you've got you know data bricks
Redis，您已经了解数据块
you've got event messaging you know I
你有事件消息，你知道我
mean just all this really good stuff
意味着所有这些非常好的东西
that you should absolutely feel free to
你应该绝对自由
look at and explore and this richness of
观察和探索，这种丰富的
options is why at the moment I should I
选择就是为什么现在我应该
should qualify because who knows you
应该有资格，因为谁认识你
know it changes every five minutes these
知道每五分钟改变一次
days things are moving
天在移动
so quickly in this particular space but
在这个特定的空间里这么快，但是
for the moment Microsoft Azur is the
目前，Microsoft Azur是
number two most prolific most sort of a
第二多产最多的一种
entrenched infrastructure as a service
根深蒂固的基础设施即服务
offering after Amazon right and so it's
提供亚马逊权利，所以它是
a it's a really compelling story there's
这是一个非常引人入胜的故事
a lot of good stuff here and obviously
这里很多好东西，显然
very few organizations understand
很少有组织了解
enterprise like Microsoft understands
像微软这样的企业了解
the enterprise right there that is that
那里的企业就是
goes without saying
一点不吭就走了
they've got a pedigree they're rivaled
他们有血统，可以与之匹敌
by very few others in the industry so
很少有其他行业
they know the use cases that enterprises
他们知道企业的用例
will care about and of course spring is
会关心的，当然春天是
is a very entrenched in enterprise as
在企业中根深蒂固
well so you know it's nice that these
好吧，你知道这些很好
integrations work so well together so
整合效果很好
what we're gonna do today is now that
我们今天要做的就是
we've got a new application up and
我们有一个新的应用程序，
running we're going to build a little
运行我们要建立一些
application that uses some of the stuff
使用一些东西的应用程序
in Microsoft Azure now you can create
现在可以在Microsoft Azure中创建
you can actually use Microsoft Azure
您可以实际使用Microsoft Azure
from the command line there's a command
从命令行有一个命令
line tool you can install on your local
您可以在本地安装的线工具
machine or just use the cloud shell so I
机器或只是使用云外壳，所以我
clicked up here and this little this
点击这里，这个小这个
little arrow and the click on that and
小箭头，然后点击
it's gonna launch the shell right here
它会在这里启动外壳
in the browser and I'll be dumped into a
在浏览器中，我将其转储到
unix linux shell that has access to the
可以访问
command line that i can then use and
我可以使用的命令行
it's already pre authenticated so I can
它已经预先认证，所以我可以
do you know I hit a Z and I get all the
你知道我碰到Z了吗
options here and so on so you can
选项等等，这样您就可以
certainly do that or you can just use
当然可以，或者您可以使用
the console the portal itself and I'm
控制台本身的门户，我
gonna just use the portal and and
只需使用门户网站，然后
because I've already pre provisioned
因为我已经预配置了
certain things here I'm not gonna spell
我这里不会拼写的某些东西
out how to provision all this stuff this
找出如何提供所有这些东西
time just because it takes a little
时间只是因为它需要一点时间
while sometimes it takes a little while
有时需要一点时间
and I don't want to chew up screen time
而且我不想浪费屏幕时间
just waiting for stuff to provision but
只是在等待东西供应
it is easy to do and you know there's a
这很容易做到，而且您知道
lot of ways to do it one thing that's
做到这一点的很多方法是
kind of interesting about Microsoft
关于微软有点有趣
Azure is that they have what are they
Azure是他们拥有什么
called a zoo or resource manager
被称为动物园或资源经理
templates or something like that arm
模板或类似的手臂
files basically basically these files
文件基本上基本上是这些文件
are the bread and butter of the platform
是平台的面包和黄油
and so there are REST API is that you
所以有REST API是
can use that take these files as inputs
可以使用将这些文件作为输入
there are there is the user interface
有用户界面
which just creates those files for you
只会为您创建这些文件
and then it transmits them as well and
然后它也传输它们
the command-line all that does behind
命令行中所有要做的事情
the scenes is it creates these resource
场景是它创造了这些资源
files so you can actually if you want to
文件，因此您实际上可以根据需要
automate things you can just get ahold
自动化您可以得到的东西
of these
这些
template files these files that are used
模板文件这些使用的文件
to describe how things should be
描述事情应该如何
provisioned and then store the version
预配，然后存储版本
control them and transmit them again
控制它们并再次传输
later and that makes it very easy to
以后，这很容易
reproduce things right the entire
完整地再现事物
platform was built that way this is
平台是这样建立的
different from for example Microsoft uh
与Microsoft uh不同
sorry different from for example AWS
抱歉与例如AWS不同
where CloudFormation was an afterthought
CloudFormation是事后的想法
it was added later on right
它是稍后添加的
so um okay what are we going to what do
所以，嗯，我们要怎么做
I do
我做
well I'm gonna build an application
好吧，我要建立一个应用程序
let's just start with the simple stuff
让我们从简单的东西开始
actually I didn't add JDBC did I I'm
实际上我没有添加JDBC，我是
gonna go ahead and add the JDBC support
继续添加JDBC支持
here in my Springwood application and oh
在我的Springwood应用程序中，哦
say dependency spring okay spring
说依赖性春天好春天
starter JDBC and again this isn't even
入门JDBC，这甚至都不是
this isn't even a spring cloud thing
这甚至不是春天的乌云
it's just regular old JP support I want
这只是我想要的常规旧JP支持
to build a use JBC and again you
建立一个使用JBC，然后你
probably used the JDBC support and
可能使用了JDBC支持，并且
spring before this is not particularly
在此之前的春天并不特别
new but what I want to do is I want to
新的，但是我想做的是
talk to sequel server which is you know
与续集服务器交谈，您知道吗
awesome I don't know if you've ever used
太棒了，我不知道你是否曾经使用过
Microsoft sequel server but I don't
Microsoft续集服务器，但我不知道
think many would deny or argue that it
认为许多人会否认或争论
is not one of the sort of gold standards
不是黄金标准之一
of sequel databases out there it has
有续集数据库
been around forever and a day it is a I
永远存在，有一天，我
think it's up there with them you know
认为和他们在一起
Oracle's Oracle's database and and
Oracle的Oracle数据库以及
Postgres as being one of the most you
Postgres被视为您中最多的人之一
know one of most fully featured
知道功能最全的之一
databases out there and here you can
数据库在那里，在这里您可以
provision a sequel server on Azur fully
在Azur上完全配置续集服务器
featured you know you can do geographic
特色，你知道你可以做地理
redundancies you can do threat
您可以做裁员的威胁
protection you can do all this sort of
保护，您可以执行所有此类操作
stuff here you configure a username and
在这里，您配置用户名和
password you give it a resource group
您为其提供资源组的密码
and the resource group is nice because
资源组很好，因为
you can you can log into your portal
您可以登录到门户
delete the resource group and then
删除资源组，然后
everything that's in there it gets
那里的一切都会得到
deleted as well so you can reset back to
也已删除，因此您可以重置回
zero with no pain at all right and you
零，没有痛苦，你
owned by oh I see that it actually
拥有的哦，我看到它实际上是
created a resource group forth for the
创建了一个资源组
storage required to store the you know
存储所需的存储空间
transy
转运
femoral log files and pids and whatever
股骨日志文件和PID以及其他内容
else is getting created in my little
别人在我的小地方被创造
cloud shell Europe here region here and
云壳欧洲在这里地区在这里和
I'm I'm actually in Zurich Switzerland
我实际上在瑞士苏黎世
as I write this so it created one in
当我写这篇文章时，它创造了一个
guess where West Europe how cool is that
猜猜西欧在哪里有多酷
huh
hu
so I'm using the boot flows or one I
所以我正在使用引导流程或一个
could do that I could create the region
可以做到，我可以创建区域
you know you can do all sorts of
你知道你可以做各种各样的事情
interesting things there automation
有趣的东西在那里自动化
options when you got there you're gonna
选择，当你到达那里，你会
have all that but I'm not gonna do that
有所有的东西，但我不会那样做
I've already got one I'm gonna click on
我已经有一个，我要点击
this instead hit okay yeah thank you
这反而好了，是的，谢谢
close that down and when I click on
关闭它，当我单击
bootiful adventures that's the server
服务器的冒险冒险
that I've got okay and the server you
我还好，服务器你
know I can configure access to it to
知道我可以配置对它的访问
Active Directory that's another thing
Active Directory是另一回事
that's compelling every organization in
这迫使每个组织
the world that I've ever with that I've
我曾经拥有的世界
ever interacted has used you know of any
曾经使用过的您都知道
size really uses active active directory
大小确实使用活动活动目录
but it is just a very entrenched
但这只是一个根深蒂固的
technology especially in larger
技术，特别是在较大的领域
organizations nowadays you see a little
当今的组织，您会看到一些
bit more Google cloud you know Google
多一点Google Cloud，您知道Google
Apps for your domain but nothing nearly
您网域的应用程式，但几乎没有
so prolific as the active directory
与活动目录一样多
suite you know the the outlook and
套房，你知道的前景和
active combination right that is the
主动组合权
most entrenched thing in the world so to
世界上最根深蒂固的东西
be able to have Active Directory in the
能够在其中拥有Active Directory
cloud to builders point-and-click and
只需点击一下云，即可向建筑商
get yourself in Active Directory that
让自己进入Active Directory
integrates with other active directories
与其他活动目录集成
and so on is unique it's valuable it's
如此独特是很有价值的
it's interesting so the fact that I can
这很有趣，所以我可以
now talk about access to my sequel
现在说说我的续集
server in terms of these access
这些访问方面的服务器
directory Active Directory roles and
目录Active Directory角色和
users and so on that's awesome I've got
用户等等，这真棒
my sequel databases to remember that one
我的续集数据库记得那个
server but I can have multiple databases
服务器，但我可以有多个数据库
here and I've got one database here
在这里，我在这里有一个数据库
called beautiful adventures now you of
现在被称为美丽的冒险
course you could create your own
当然你可以创建自己的
database so this is my server I'm gonna
数据库，所以这是我的服务器
go to here click new database and when
转到这里单击新数据库，何时
you do that you can provision a database
您可以设置数据库
name and then you can provision a source
名称，然后您可以提供来源
and you can see you can click you can
然后您可以看到可以单击
configure a blank one but what I did and
配置一个空白但我做了什么
literally all that I did was to create a
实际上，我所做的就是创建一个
sample using adventureworks
使用Adventureworks进行采样
LT which is a fully featured schema that
LT是功能齐全的架构，
has some sample data in it with which
里面有一些样本数据
you can or
你可以或
you can configure that you want this to
您可以配置您希望它
be an elastic secret pool you can
成为一个有弹性的秘密池
configure the pricing tier you can
配置您可以的定价层
configure the collation I mean all that
配置整理我的意思是
kind of stuff that you want and then you
你想要的东西然后你
get a database I've already done that
得到一个数据库，我已经做到了
of course okay I've already done that so
当然可以，我已经这样做了
here is my database where ours my
这是我的数据库
database I just lost it
数据库我刚丢了
sequel databases beautiful adventures
续集数据库美丽的冒险
click on this and now I'm given
点击这个，现在我得到了
information about the database itself
有关数据库本身的信息
I've used a total of my 11 gigabytes SR
我已经用完了11 GB的SR
11 megabytes of space out of my maximum
我的最大空间不足11兆字节
250 gig so I think I'll be fine I'll
250演出，我想我会没事的
think I'll be for this particular demo
认为我会参加这个特定的演示
for this screencast I think I'm well
对于这个截屏视频，我认为我很好
within safe levels okay I don't think
在安全范围内，好吧，我不认为
I'm gonna need more but look at this
我需要更多，但看看这个
there's there's some really nice things
有一些很棒的东西
here I was just talking to people on
在这里我只是在和别人聊天
Twitter about this the other day and one
Twitter关于这一天和一个
thing that post quiz doesn't seem to
测验似乎没有的事情
have yet that some organizations love is
还有些组织喜欢的是
transparent data encryption this is one
透明数据加密，这是一种
of the things that really really
真的真的
expensive databases like Oracle and of
昂贵的数据库，例如Oracle和
course things like sequel server have
当然，诸如续集服务器之类的东西
out of the box that is to say you can
开箱即用，可以
have the database configure encryption
让数据库配置加密
for your data in the database right this
对于您数据库中的数据吧
is even more critical today in the world
在当今世界上更加重要
of you know security hacks and
你们当中的一些人知道安全性
everything being vulnerable these kinds
一切都容易受到伤害
of things are just there you just
事情就在那里
automatically get them for free by using
通过使用自动免费获得它们
these fully managed scale backed up
这些完全托管的规模备份
services and these are valuable so there
服务，这些都很有价值，所以在那里
you go we've got we've got a sequel
你走了，我们有续集了
database I'm going to use the query
数据库，我要使用查询
editor here I have a configuration file
编辑器在这里我有一个配置文件
so I'm gonna copy this configuration
所以我要复制此配置
file desktop misc or not
文件桌面是否杂项
oh I put it in here didn't I couldn't
哦，我把它放在这里，我不能
figs there we go
无花果我们去
as you heard uh properties I'm gonna
如你所知，我会
copy that you source main resources
复制您的主要资源
application dot properties okay and I am
应用点属性还可以，我是
going to delete everything in that
将删除其中的所有内容
resource coop just like we talked about
就像我们在谈论资源合作
as soon as I'm done with this so I've
一旦完成此操作，我就
got this configuration here here are my
在这里得到这个配置是我的
keys and bat and passwords and all that
键，蝙蝠和密码以及所有其他内容
kind of stuff
一种东西
um I have a password spring time for my
嗯，我有一个春季密码
sequel database so I'll log in there and
续集数据库，所以我将在那里登录
I get this nice editor I can actually
我得到了这个好编辑器，我实际上可以
log in and interact with the data and
登录并与数据交互并
the tables and all that I've got tables
桌子和我所有的桌子
I've got views and I've got stored
我有意见，而且已经储存
procedures all of which I can work with
我可以使用的所有程序
here right so I'm gonna say select all
在这里，所以我要说全选
from sales Lt customer okay it go run
来自销售Lt客户，好的，可以运行
okay
好的
it gives me all the data there's
它给了我所有的数据
actually a fair bit more data here than
实际上，这里的数据要比
I want so I'm going to use the sequel
我想要，所以我要使用续集
server variant of limits it's like top
极限的服务器变体就像top
ten for example okay get that back or
例如十点好吧，把它拿回来
you can just select top five get that
您可以选择前五名
back there we go that fits into a nice
回到那里，我们去适合一个不错的
simple range I've got a customer ID a
简单的范围，我有一个客户ID
first name and last name field that I
我的名字和姓氏字段
want to I want to observe so let's use
想我想观察，让我们使用
that these are for customer records okay
这些是供客户记录的
so let's quit a thing that manages
所以让我们退出一个可以管理的事情
customer data
客户资料
okay so class sequel server demo okay
好的，所以上课续集服务器演示好了
and event listener application ready
和事件监听器应用程序就绪
event
事件
already application ready event okay and
已经准备好应用程序事件，并且
um this will be a demo that demonstrates
嗯，这将是一个演示
how to use sequel server and that's
如何使用续集服务器，那就是
nothing special we're just gonna use the
没什么特别的，我们只是要使用
regular spring JDBC template to do that
常规的Spring JDBC模板来做到这一点
okay so as normal it's gonna be a
好吧，像往常一样，它将是
regular spring bean so we'll make it a
普通的四季豆，所以我们将其制成
component like so we're gonna create a
像这样的组件，我们将创建一个
sequel query private my computer's
续集查询私人我的电脑
dragging because I'm using QuickTime
拖曳，因为我使用的是QuickTime
okay there's my query very simple
好的，我的查询非常简单
couldn't get simpler and I'm going to
变得简单，我要
create a I'm gonna inject my JDBC
创建一个我要注入我的JDBC
template and quit inject that into the
模板并退出，将其注入到
constructor okay and all I'm gonna do is
构造函数好吧，我要做的就是
I'm gonna load the records in the
我要将记录加载到
database and then you know print them
数据库，然后知道打印它们
out so public static class customer
出去，所以公共静态类的客户
would be a data class with all the
将是具有所有
Constructors no arts constructors all
构造函数所有艺术构造函数
that kind of stuff private string ID
那种东西的私有字符串ID
we're gonna call it customer ID private
我们将其称为私人客户ID
string first name last name all right
字符串名字姓氏
there we are and I'm gonna map that data
我们在那里，我要映射该数据
so I'm gonna create a row map are here
所以我要在这里创建一个行图
okay
好的
row mapper up type of customer new row
客户新行的行映射器类型
member okay and my job is going to be
成员好，我的工作将是
very simple when I'm given a result set
得到结果集时非常简单
at a certain offset which is indicated
以一定的偏移量表示
by row numb I'm gonna turn it into a
逐行麻木，我要把它变成一个
custom object so RS get long customer ID
自定义对象，以便RS获得较长的客户ID
RS doc and get to string first name RS
RS doc并获取字符串名字RS
get string last name all right there's
得到字符串姓氏好吧
my simple roam effort
我简单的漫游工作
did I say string I meant long alright
我说的字符串我是说好吗
good stuff good stuff so there's my
好东西好东西所以有我的
simple remember that of course can be
简单记住，当然可以
written as a lambda which is nice and
写为lambda，这很好，而且
then I'm gonna use the JDBC template
然后我将使用JDBC模板
I'll say this EW September query this
我会说这个九月电子战
Cleary Rome Apple okay and you know I
Cleary Rome Apple可以，你知道我
suppose I could just put all that in the
假设我可以将所有内容放入
method itself it's just gonna run once
方法本身只会运行一次
after all doesn't really matter stuff
毕竟不是很重要的东西
almost redundant I could have just
几乎多余，我本来可以
inlined it for that matter but it's
就此而言，它是内联的，但是
easier to read
更容易阅读
I think broken out like this especially
我认为特别是这样爆发
with my font size being so so large so
我的字体太大了
as to benefit our our viewers on YouTube
使我们的YouTube观众受益
and so on customer list that for each
以此类推的客户清单
and I'm just gonna log out the result
我将注销结果
turn time I'm gonna use the log4j logger
该轮到我要使用log4j记录器了
that I've got here and then right you
我来这里然后对你
know inject that okay so there we go
知道注入那好吧，所以我们去了
there's my logger
有我的记录器
there's my application I'm just gonna
有我的申请
print out the data in the database when
打印出数据库中的数据时
the application starts up so we'll go
该应用程序启动，所以我们去
ahead and run this now and see what we
继续并立即运行此命令，看看我们
get in order for this to work notice
得到这个工作通知
that we've got here a you know spring
我们到了这里，你知道春天
that data source that username and
该数据源，用户名和
password and so on I got the URL here by
密码等等，我在这里获得了网址
the way let me go ahead and start this
让我继续前进的方式
while we're waiting I'll talk about the
在等待的过程中，我将讨论
configuration here so I've got the URL
在这里配置，所以我有URL
and the URL you can get by going into
以及您可以通过以下方式获得的网址
your database here and you go to and if
您的数据库在这里，如果
you figure I'm always I always forget
你想我总是我总是忘记
about that they seem to keep the
关于他们似乎保持
credentials and the relevant information
凭证和相关信息
under different screens no that's
在不同的屏幕下，不是
definitely not it so we go to sequel
绝对不是，所以我们去续集
databases
资料库
click on that and connection strings
点击那个和连接字符串
that one's pretty straightforward isn't
那不是很简单
it look at that so there's the
它看着，所以有
connection string for a do net JDBC ODBC
NET JDBC ODBC的连接字符串
the idiota net is the way you can fix
idiota网是您可以解决的方法
the framework for connecting the
连接的框架
databases in net you know Microsoft on
您知道Microsoft的网络中的数据库
that platform ODBC is the Windows
该平台ODBC是Windows
database connectivity API it's an
数据库连接API
abstraction that's into Windows although
Windows中的抽象
I think now you can actually talk to
我想现在你可以和
that you can use the same SPI in Linux
您可以在Linux中使用相同的SPI
in certain cases and then there's this
在某些情况下，这是
thing called pH he whatever that is and
所谓的pH值，无论是什么
then JDBC okay and JDBC is what we're
那么JDBC还可以，而JDBC是我们要做的
gonna we've already got this here notice
我们已经在这里收到通知了
that the password is not specified right
没有指定密码正确
so you have to actually plug that in and
所以您必须将其实际插入
I I actually did I just said I jerked
我实际上只是说我抽搐了
the thing that it gave me with I just
它带给我的东西
added a dollar sign and I just said
加了一个美元符号，我刚才说
sequel server password and that's
续集服务器密码，那就是
actually the sequel server password from
实际上是来自的续集服务器密码
here right that's actually you know
在这里，实际上你知道
encoded although you don't need to do
编码，尽管您不需要
that I could just specify the password
我可以只指定密码
value like spring that dates first up
像春天这样的价值首先出现
password okay so there's that now we've
密码好，所以现在我们有了
got that what happened here oh I need to
知道这里发生的事情哦，我需要
comment out some of the stuff that we're
评论一些我们正在做的事情
not using just yet because otherwise
暂时不使用，因为否则
it's not gonna work so good okay there's
它不会工作的很好，好吧
my sequel server okay
我的续集服务器还可以
Oh something's running on that port
哦，那个端口上正在运行
isn't it okay let's see
好吗，让我们看看
JPS such a Java process killer kill 87
JPS这样的Java进程杀手kill杀87
302 attack it there how embarrassing
302攻击那里有多么尴尬
- of 987 302 haha okay take two
-987302中的-哈哈，好了再拿两个
now I've got a so right now I'm using
现在我有一个所以现在我正在使用
spring boot to 8:06 and I'm using that
春天引导到8:06，我正在使用
because while we have spring boot to
因为虽然我们有 spring boot
that one and spring boot to that one is
那一个和那个的弹簧靴是
compatible with Java eleven and all that
与Java 11兼容
good stuff the spring integration from
春天整合的好东西
accept Azure isn't yet compatible it's
接受Azure尚不兼容
been weak to that one so I'm using 2006
对此很弱，所以我用的是2006
spring 2006 is creaking the old it's
2006年春季正在破旧
like like a month old at this point I
就像现在一个月大
mean it is it is ancient but you know
是说它很古老，但是你知道
that's okay we're gonna use Java 8
没关系，我们将使用Java 8
instead of Java 11 and then when the
而不是Java 11，然后
spring boot to that one supporting
弹簧靴到那个支撑
release of the spring integration for
发布用于
spring from acceptor sewer is released
受体下水道的弹簧释放
then we can rerun this program in Java
然后我们可以用Java重新运行该程序
11 and everything should just be fine in
11一切都应该很好
the meantime we get issues about missing
同时，我们遇到了有关失踪的问题
Jax Jax be types like java xml bind data
Jax Jax是Java xml绑定数据之类的类型
convert them already let's see what we
转换他们已经让我们看看我们
got now look at that huh there's our
现在看看那个，那是我们的
data of course there's the first 5
数据当然有前5个
records you know gee harris careers
记录您知道gee harris的职业
gates harrington etc okay um so that's
盖茨·哈灵顿等，好吧，那是
this okay we've got that now next thing
好的，我们现在有了下一个东西
you know I love sequel server it is
你知道我喜欢续集服务器
recompiling as we discuss there's some
当我们讨论时重新编译
really nice features including things
非常好的功能，包括东西
like TDE for you know transparent data
就像TDE，因为您知道透明数据
encryption for address security great I
加密以提高地址安全性I
love that that's it you know you could
爱那就是你知道你可以
run it yourself you shouldn't I mean you
自己运行它，我不应该是你
could why why would you want to run your
可以为什么你为什么要运行你的
own sequel server when you can get
自己的续集服务器何时可以获得
Microsoft to do it for you but you could
Microsoft为您做，但是您可以
run that yourself right arguably what
可以说正确地运行自己
what I want when I go to a public cloud
当我去公共云时我想要什么
I want to take advantage of things that
我想利用那些
are really unique things like cosmos and
是真正独特的事物，例如宇宙和
cosmos is a a database that speaks
cosmos是一个可以说的数据库
multiple protocols you can talk to it to
您可以与之对话的多种协议
Cassandra
卡桑德拉
through MongoDB through sequel api's and
通过续集API通过MongoDB和
it can model data in a number of
它可以对许多数据进行建模
different ways I've got a sequel I've
我有续集的不同方式
got a cosmos DB instance here it's
在这里有一个宇宙数据库实例
geographically distributed it's highly
地域分布很高
available easily to replicate I can
可以轻松复制我可以
actually see this I'm not sure if you
真的看到了，我不确定你是否
can see that if I click on the region
可以看到，如果我单击该区域
configuration here I can now my mouse
现在可以在这里配置我的鼠标
let me see if I think it's a little
让我看看我是否认为这有点
larger for you
给你更大
mm-hmm I've got two instances of this
嗯，我有两个实例
data right and right now they're
现在和现在的数据
configured in Australia because when I
在澳大利亚配置，因为当我
cook when I configure them I was in
当我配置它们时做饭
Australia I'm gonna go ahead and just
澳大利亚我要继续前进
remove one of them there you go it's no
删除其中一个就可以了
longer my data is no longer available in
我的数据不再可用
that region but I'm gonna make one
该地区，但我要成为一个
available here in where am i I'm in
我在哪里
Zurich so West Europe let's do that
苏黎世，西欧让我们做到这一点
there we go now I've got geographically
现在我们要走了
distributed data in two different
以两种不同的方式分发数据
regions in the world just as simple as
世界上的区域就像
that I might go ahead and remove it from
我可能会继续将其从
Australia there we go
澳大利亚我们去
okay um so that's that that's all you
好的，那就是你的全部
need to do to get data you know
需要做以获取您知道的数据
consistently available across different
始终可以在不同的地方使用
regions and they're billable of course
地区，它们当然要收费
through the through my my account one
通过我的我的帐户
thing I should stress I didn't really
我应该强调的是我并不是真的
talk about this but I'm pretty sure that
谈论这个，但我很确定
I saw somewhere that Microsoft Azur
我在某处看到了Microsoft Azur
has the most regions in the world that
在世界上拥有最多的地区
is to say whoops I need to have two
就是说我需要两个
regions do I let's do that hit save
区域，让我们点击保存
I'm not sure what I just did discard
我不确定我刚刚丢弃了什么
okay let's add this over it save okay
好吧，我们在上面加上这个保存吧
I'm adding a region I think you need to
我要添加一个我认为您需要
add a region before you can remove
在删除之前添加区域
something um okay
嗯嗯
are we happy looks like we're happy now
我们快乐吗看起来像我们现在快乐
can I remove one
我可以删除一个
oh it's updating so now it's doing the
哦，它正在更新，所以现在它正在
writes it's actually doing it you know
写它实际上是在做你知道的
replication Microsoft DOS uber has more
复制Microsoft DOS uber具有更多功能
regions and I think any other cloud
地区，我认为还有其他云
vendor that's what I saw at least I'm
我至少看到的是供应商
happy to be wrong on that but they have
很高兴在这方面犯错，但他们有
a really really large list of regions
很大的区域列表
available they even have a a region
可用，他们甚至有一个地区
available in China now this isn't
现在在中国没有
strictly speaking Microsoft Azure it's a
严格来说，Microsoft Azure是一个
because of the way it's because the way
因为这是因为
people have to do business in China
人们必须在中国做生意
it's a white label version of Microsoft
这是微软的白标版本
Azure that runs on a cloud that isn't
在非云上运行的Azure
Microsoft but it is as it were and it's
微软，但事实如此，
you know six and a half of one or have
你知道一个的六个半或有
to have to have a dozen of the other
必须要有十几个其他
it's the same thing it's just not quite
是同一件事，只是不完全是
the same thing okay and charge
相同的事情可以并且收费
differently there's certain data
不同的是某些数据
provenance rule that are different there
那里的出处规则不同
but the fact is it's there right you can
但事实是你可以在那里
talk you can use and rely on these api's
谈谈您可以使用并依赖这些api的
in just all sorts of regions there's I
在各种各样的地区，我
think there's a government compliant one
认为有一个政府合规的
US government compliant one I mean a
美国政府合规的一个意思是
German compliant one there's all sorts
德国合规的种类繁多
of new regions so that's doing its thing
的新区域，这就是它正在做的事情
right now it's updating we'll see what
现在它正在更新，我们将看到
happens the fact that it is just a few
发生这样的事实，那就是少数
buttons to to make that work that speaks
按钮以使说话的作品
to why cosmos is so amazing right um I
为什么宇宙如此神奇呢？
have some collections I've got some data
有一些收藏，我有一些数据
here I'm gonna browse the data while
在这里，我将浏览数据，而
that's doing its work and I can see how
这是它的工作，我可以看到
much data I've got I've got this
我有很多数据我有这个
reservations collection okay what I want
预订集合好我想要什么
to do is I know I want to talk to that
我知道我想跟那个说话
data using the cosmos TV swing data
宇宙电视摇摆数据的数据
integration okay so if I click on this
整合还可以，如果我点击这个
okay let's see what we got here I can
好吧，让我们看看我们能到达这里
add collection
添加收藏
I can click on the existing collections
我可以点击现有收藏集
I can see the documents in that
我可以看到其中的文件
collection now this is weird documents
现在收集，这是奇怪的文件
and collections feel like MongoDB and
和集合感觉就像MongoDB和
yet I've got records here that look like
但我这里有记录，看起来像
MongoDB saan document but I can query it
MongoDB saan文档，但我可以查询它
using a sequel query right or a stored
使用续集查询权限或存储的
procedure you know lots of options UDF
程序，您知道很多选择UDF
trigger a new sequel query lots of
触发一个新的续集查询
different interesting things you can do
您可以做的各种有趣的事情
here I've got some records here I'm
我在这里有一些记录
gonna go ahead and delete all the data
继续删除所有数据
okay oh you know what I could use to
好吧，哦，你知道我可以用来
make this easier I can use the Azure
使这更容易，我可以使用Azure
Microsoft storage Explorer now the
Microsoft Storage Explorer现在
storage Explorer is a separate electron
存储资源管理器是一个单独的电子
based application that runs separately
基于应用程序，可单独运行
right and you can use it to talk to
对的，你可以用它来和
among other things your your Azure
除其他外，您的Azure
storage account and your cosmos DB
存储帐户和您的cosmos数据库
document which is pretty cool so now I
文档非常酷，所以现在我
can log into that go into the document
可以登录到该文件
their documents and delete does that
他们的文件并删除
work
工作
well yes yeah okay delete that I thought
是的，是的，好的，删除我以为
I can bulk select them but but uh
我可以批量选择它们，但是
doesn't matter what I'm doing is I'm
我在做什么都没关系
deleting the data in the storage in this
在此删除存储中的数据
storage Explorer and now if I go back to
存储资源管理器，现在，如果我返回到
here and do a refresh refresh come on
在这里做刷新刷新来
there you go you can see there's nothing
你去那里你可以看到没有任何东西
left okay
还好吧
okay so now I want to use the same thing
好吧，现在我要使用相同的东西
when I use the same information document
当我使用相同的信息文档时
in the same cosmos to be account and
在同一个宇宙中被考虑
talk to it from my spring application
从我的春季申请中谈谈
meanwhile you can see that the read and
同时您可以看到阅读和
write locations are now available in
现在可以在以下位置找到写入位置
France Central Australia south east and
法国中部澳大利亚东南部和
west so I'm going to go back to this and
西，所以我要回到这个
disable two of the other ones because I
禁用其他两个，因为我
don't want all those I just need a few
不想所有那些我只需要几个
of them I just need one I'll take Europe
其中我只需要一个我就带欧洲
that's fine so we're gonna go ahead and
很好，我们要继续
delete uh Australia's East
删除澳洲东部
okay and then get rid of that one as
好吧，然后摆脱那个
well it's save so my date has been moved
好吧，保存，所以我的约会已被移动
to France central of course there is no
到法国中央当然没有
data so I suspect that makes the
数据，所以我怀疑这使得
migration even easier I'm gonna go back
迁移更容易，我要回去
to the database the cosmos DB database
到数据库cosmos DB数据库
here and I'm gonna now write some data
在这里，我现在要写一些数据
now I'm gonna be kind of interested to
现在我会对
see what that looks like if I start
看看我开始的样子
writing data to this while I'm deleting
在删除数据时为此写入数据
one of the other regions but anyway we
其他地区之一，但无论如何我们
can do that very easily thanks to the
可以很容易地做到这一点
spring data integration so I have a data
春天的数据集成，所以我有一个数据
of type reservation and I'll make this a
类型保留，我将其设为
a data object it's gonna be something
数据对象
Lombok to handle compile time
龙目岛（Lombok）处理编译时间
annotations and that kind of thing it's
注释之类的东西
gonna be a table
会成为一张桌子
document no it's a table I need to add
文档否，这是我需要添加的表格
alright I need to add the swing boot
好吧，我需要添加秋千靴
comes to be starter so let's go back to
成为入门者，让我们回到
my build here and I'm going to add the
我的构建在这里，我要添加
cosmos starter to my build and the
宇宙初学者到我的构建和
cosmos starter always eludes me it is
宇宙启动器总是让我难以理解
Azure human DB spring group starter calm
Azure Human DB Spring组入门者沉着
Microsoft Azure voila okay and that's
Microsoft Azure，好吧，那就是
managed for us by the
由我们为我们管理
Microsoft bombed as or spring bomb Bill
微软轰炸成法案
of Materials made and build so with that
材料的制造和建造
in place I can create a table or a
我可以在适当的位置创建表格或
document so yeah it's a doctor document
是的，这是医生的文件
and the collection name will be
集合名称将为
reservations all right all right have a
保留所有权利保留所有权利
document of type of string ID and
字符串ID和类型的文档
another one this field is named okay I
这个字段的另一个名字叫好
can call this reservation name and I
可以叫这个预订名，我
could map it to a column I want to do
可以将其映射到我想做的一列
it's not just me I think let's just go
我认为我们不只是我
see what I've got here browse
看看我在这里有什么浏览
collections I suppose it doesn't really
我想这不是真的
matter because we've got no data in
很重要，因为我们没有数据
there so it's it's ragged let's just
在那里，这是衣衫agged的，让我们只是
make it make it a name there this is the
让它成为一个名字那里是
ID and there we go there's our simple
ID，我们去了，这很简单
entity and I'm gonna create a repository
实体，我要创建一个存储库
amenda that's a reservation repository
amenda是一个预订库
extends the document DB repository and
扩展文档数据库存储库，并
the entity of the type reservation whose
类型预订的实体，其
keys a type of spring and by the way I'm
键入一种弹簧，顺便说一句
using spring data cosmos time spring is
使用弹簧数据宇宙时间弹簧是
spring data document DB support here
spring数据文档数据库支持在这里
there I could have used spring data JPA
在那里我可以使用Spring数据JPA
for example using sequel server and one
例如使用续集服务器和一个
thing I could have also done with sequel
我本可以用续集来做的事情
server in particular is I could use the
服务器特别是我可以使用
r2 DBC support so our two DBC github.com
r2 DBC支持，所以我们两个DBC github.com
get our two DBC our two DBC is a
得到我们两个DBC我们两个DBC是一个
reactive sequel data access spi and
反应性续集数据访问SPI和
right now there is features again these
现在又有这些功能
are talking to natively reactive sequel
在谈论本机反应性续集
database drivers supporting h2
支持h2的数据库驱动程序
supporting Postgres and supporting just
支持Postgres和支持
last week microsoft sequel server so I
上周微软续集服务器，所以我
could do a reactive sequel server you
可以做一个反应性续集服务器
know integration here
在这里知道整合
as well right that's pretty much that
正确的就是
that would be supported in the new
新版本会支持
spring data JDBC and for both sequel and
Spring数据JDBC以及续集和
for both reactive and nonreactive
适用于反应性和非反应性
variants okay so anyway spring data
变体还可以，所以无论如何弹簧数据
document DB I've got a repository and
文档数据库我有一个存储库，
now same as before I'm gonna use a
现在和以前一样，我要使用
cosmos DB demo I'm gonna write some data
cosmos DB演示，我要写一些数据
to the database it's gonna be a beam
到数据库将是一束光芒
that starts up listens on listens for an
启动时会监听
event listener application ready event
事件侦听器应用程序就绪事件
class public void demo okay throws
类公共无效演示好抛出
exception at component private final and
组件private final和
here I'm gonna inject my reservation
在这里我要注入我的预订
repository okay I'm gonna write some
好的，我要写一些
data that's actually create that check
实际创建该检查的数据
that in the constructor and we'll write
在构造函数中，我们将编写
some data so steam dot o a b c dot map
一些数据，所以蒸汽点oabc点图
name new reservation no name okay and
命名新的预订，没有名字，好
then map are this done RR dot save r dot
然后映射完成RR点保存r点
for each log info okay and as before i'm
对于每个日志信息都可以，就像我之前一样
gonna use Lombok to create my little
要用龙目岛创造我的小
longer there and that's it no you know i
在那里更长，那是不，你知道我
also want to delete the data I don't
也想删除我不想要的数据
have duplicate data before so this time
之前有重复的数据，所以这次
dot RR dot Toledo okay so there we go
点RR点托莱多好吧，我们去了
there's our delete all and then we're
有我们的全部删除，然后我们
gonna write some data to Davis let's
要写一些数据到戴维斯，让我们
restart this in order for that to work
重新启动它以使其正常工作
we need to cosmos DB configuration I'm
我们需要宇宙数据库配置
gonna tell it what URI
要告诉它什么URI
key and database to use like so that's
密钥和数据库使用像这样
we can get that information by going
我们可以通过以下方式获取该信息
into our portal going to us 0 cosmos DB
进入我们的门户去给我们0 cosmos DB
and you can see here when I click on
当我单击时，您可以在此处看到
this it shows me keys these keys or what
它显示了这些键或什么
I need to get the information so there's
我需要获取信息，所以有
my URI my primary key and my secondary
我的URI我的主键和我的辅助键
key my primary
关键我的主要
string and so on all that fits into this
字符串等等都适合这个
and of course the name of the database
当然还有数据库的名称
is self-evident cosmos TV reservations
是不言而喻的宇宙电视预订
okay so with that in place we can now
好吧，有了它，我们现在可以
restart the application and now we
重新启动应用程序，现在我们
should see not just our sequel server
应该不仅看到我们的续集服务器
data but our cosmos DB dab data to
数据，但我们的cosmos DB dab数据
different types of databases each of
每个数据库都有不同类型的数据库
which we can talk to in very idiomatic
我们可以很习惯地与之交谈
spring style
春天风格
okay
好的
now hopefully that's that query is much
现在希望这是很多查询
faster oh it is look at that okay I got
快点哦，看得到
the cosmos TV data immediately I mean it
我马上就知道了宇宙电视数据
was really quick there it is there's my
真的很快，那里是我的
three records and we should now if I go
三个记录，现在我应该去
to the portal I go here
到门户我去这里
cosmos TV go there go to the documents
宇宙电视去那里去文件
browse collections document Explorer
浏览收藏文档浏览器
there we go there's our three records a
我们去那里有我们的三个记录
and here's C and there's B huh not bad
这是C，还有B，还不错
so okay we've got cosmos we've got
好吧，我们有了宇宙，我们有了
sequel server what else can we do well
续集服务器我们还能做些什么
what if I want to store actual binary
如果我想存储实际的二进制文件怎么办
data you know here I've got you know
你知道的数据我知道了
highly available highly consistent data
高度可用的高度一致的数据
access for you no records but what if I
没有记录，但是如果我访问，该怎么办
have just unstructured blobs of data you
仅有非结构化的数据块
know well here I can use the Microsoft
我很清楚这里可以使用Microsoft
object storage service right the so
对象存储服务没错
that's easy enough to do we just need to
这很容易做到，我们只需要
bring in the right dependency here so we
在这里引入正确的依赖关系，所以我们
bring in Azur document DB Springwood
引入Azur文件DB Springwood
starter add that to the application and
入门者将其添加到应用程序中
here I'm just gonna write some data
在这里我要写一些数据
let's you know let's imagine I've got a
让我们知道，让我们想象一下
a photo of a cat that I want to store
我要存储的猫的照片
and I do happen to have a photo of a cat
我碰巧有一只猫的照片
that I want to store here go to the cat
我想在这里存储去猫
there it is that's my cat it's a fat fat
那是我的猫，那是脂肪
fat cat it's a blob and we're gonna use
肥猫这是一团斑点，我们要用
a blob storage service that's that's
Blob存储服务就是这样
kind of nice we're gonna upload this cat
很好，我们要上传这只猫
in to download source resources okay
可以下载源代码了
Kate and I'm gonna now upload that cat
凯特和我现在要上传那只猫
to the storage service now of course I
我现在当然要去存储服务
already have a my storage account I can
我已经有我的存储帐户了
look at the storage account here I can
可以在这里查看存储帐户
see I've got blob containers and I've
看到我有斑点容器，
got file shares refresh right what is
得到文件共享刷新正确是什么
this that's the data no I want the
这就是数据，我不想要
blobs files there we are and this this
Blobs文件在那里，我们这个
is nice I can actually take all that I
很好，我实际上可以拿走我所有的东西
need it just to eat and you even have
只需要吃饭就可以吃
soft Denise did you see that that's
软丹妮丝，你看到那是
pretty cool
很酷
now I could here's what I want to do I
现在我可以在这里做我想做的事
want to I could just drag and drop right
想要我可以直接拖放
queue uploaded I just drag and drop from
队列上传我只是拖放
my desktop and there's the cat it's now
我的桌面上有只猫
available in the object storage service
在对象存储服务中可用
I'm gonna delete it again because I want
我要再次删除它，因为我想要
to do they I'll upload it myself right
做他们，我会自己上传
it's still uploading okay yeah so I'm
它仍在上传，是的，所以我
gonna now delete it but you know it's a
现在将其删除，但您知道它是一个
storage service is really convenient you
仓储服务真的很方便
can upload stuff I am going to write
可以上传我要写的东西
some code using the object storage
一些使用对象存储的代码
service in Microsoft Azure to upload the
Microsoft Azure中的服务以上传
code to upload that cat manually okay so
手动上传猫的代码好吗
let's do that
让我们做
right now we're gonna create a well
现在我们要制造一口井
first of all do I already have a storage
首先我已经有一个存储了
I think I already have the storage
我想我已经有存储了
starter I think that was one of the few
入门者，我认为那是少数几个
that we had on the spring and your sizer
我们在春天和你的尺码
already yep there it is okay we can go
是的，我们可以走了
back here and create a class object
回到这里并创建一个类对象
storage store rate service demo at
的存储商店费率服务演示
component at log4j - okay and here we're
log4j的组件-好的，在这里
gonna create a object storage of demo
要创建演示的对象存储
and what I'm going to do and write data
以及我要做什么和写数据
to the database using the free auto
使用免费自动访问数据库
configured cloud storage account that
配置的云存储帐户
we're gonna configure in a moment here
我们将在这里配置
we're gonna inject a resource this is
我们将注入一个资源
the Spring Framework resource it's a
Spring Framework资源是
thing that manages it's an abstraction
管理它的东西是抽象的
or on things that can produce bytes
或会产生字节的东西
basically sources of data and sinks of
基本上是数据来源和
data and we're going to inject that's
数据，我们将注入
okay CSA and resource will be a cat okay
CSA和资源都可以了
so this doc resource equals cat this dot
所以这个文档资源等于这个点
cloud storage account we go si si there
云存储帐户我们去那里
we are now which cat you might ask well
我们现在是您可能会问的那只猫
this cat the cat that we have in the
这只猫，我们在里面的猫
craft path so when I say class path
工艺路线，所以当我说课程路径时
cat PNG or jpg there it is okay so
猫PNG或jpg没关系，所以
there's our cat and we're gonna write
有我们的猫，我们要写
that data to the database when the event
该事件发生时将数据发送到数据库
listener gets called all right sorry
听众打来的电话好不好意思
it's a storage service when the event
这是事件发生时的存储服务
listener gets called public void demo
侦听器被称为public void演示
throws exception okay um and we're gonna
抛出异常好吧，我们要
use our particular our particular blob
用我们特定的斑点
container right until the where did I
直到我在哪里的容器
put it where's my storage service over
放在我的存储服务在哪里
here we use this you can see I've got
在这里我们用这个你可以看到我
the storage account I've got this
我有这个存储帐户
account here called bootiful cats and
这里的帐户称为“战利品猫”和
I've got a blob container inside that
我里面有一个斑点容器
called files think of it like a bucket
被调用的文件将其视为一个存储桶
okay and I'm gonna use the files blob
好的，我要使用文件Blob
container to write this file to the 2d
将此文件写入2D的容器
database okay today's sword service so
数据库还可以，今天的剑服务如此
in order to do that I need to get a
为了做到这一点，我需要得到一个
reference to that blob container and the
引用该Blob容器和
way I do that is I create a blob client
我这样做的方式是创建一个Blob客户端
using the storage account so this doc
使用存储帐户，因此此文档
get blob that's a great well yeah there
变得斑点很好耶
we go doc get to contain a reference to
我们去文档包含对
the files okay and what does that give
文件还可以，这有什么用
us well it gives us an exception first
我们很好，它首先给我们带来了例外
of all but also it gives us a cloud blob
总而言之，它也给我们带来了云朵斑点
container all right so I'm going to
容器没事，所以我要去
store that for later
储存以备后用
this does box okay okay
这确实框好吧好吧
good all right so there's that and we're
好吧，就是这样，我们
going to write some data to Davies we're
要向戴维斯写一些数据
gonna write some data database to the
要写一些数据数据库到
storage service um I think by the way
嗯，我想存储服务
I'm pretty sure I don't know let's
我很确定我不知道让我们
Google okay I don't know does uh how's
Google好吧，我不知道嗯
your storage service s3 does it support
您的存储服务s3是否支持
the s3 protocol yeah no it does not
s3协议是的，不是
oh wait a minute is that true there are
哦等一下那是真的
ways to do it look there's an s3 proxy
的方法看起来有一个S3代理
so if you are using the Amazon s3 API
因此，如果您使用的是Amazon s3 API
it's possible to to then use that to
然后可以使用它来
write data to the object storage service
将数据写入对象存储服务
I'm not sure if that's natively
我不确定那是不是本地人
supported now or not but the point is
现在是否支持，但重点是
you can think of this like Amazon s3
您可以像Amazon s3这样想到
okay it's just available fee all right
好吧，这只是可用的费用
so now we're gonna use the files
现在我们要使用这些文件
reference so this type files dot get
参考，以便此类型文件点获取
blocked blob reference I love that word
Blob参考被阻止，我喜欢那个词
by the way block blob cat create a
顺便说一句，阻止斑点猫创建一个
unique file name dot - string dot jpg
唯一文件名点-字符串点jpg
okay what blob reference great I'm going
好的，我要使用什么Blob参考
to use a block block reference to upload
使用块块引用上传
our data which data well the data in the
我们的数据哪些数据很好
input stream from the cat reference okay
来自猫参考的输入流还可以
and we're gonna say in I'm gonna use
我们会说我会用
this data resource stuck content length
此数据资源卡住的内容长度
to figure out how much data to upload
找出要上传多少数据
good okay and now I'm gonna write I'm
好吧，现在我要写我
gonna reflect I'm gonna log out the
会反映出我要登出
location of that uploaded block block
该上传的区块的位置
uploaded block bulb to Bach blob
将块状灯泡上载到巴赫blob
reference dot gets toward your eye okay
参考点朝向您的眼睛好吗
so that's gonna upload a new file every
这样就可以每次上传一个新文件
time we run this little program okay so
时候我们运行这个小程序好吧
let's restart that and see what we get
让我们重新启动，看看我们得到了什么
already so
已经如此
oh I don't have the configuration and as
哦，我没有配置和
I always forget so I need to have the
我总是忘记了，所以我需要
storage connection there's my connection
存储连接就是我的连接
string I'll restart this with that done
字符串，我将在完成后重新启动
but we'll go investigate where we can
但是我们会去调查
find that if you want to do it yourself
发现如果您想自己做
so you go to the storage accounts you
所以你去存储帐户
can see it's as beautiful cats here I
可以看到这里的猫就像我
can see the access keys click on that I
可以看到访问键，点击我
have wow there's all the information you
哇，有你的所有信息
would need to go to talk to that
需要去谈谈
particular hand room ok to have storage
特别的手间可以储存
service ok so did we upload the yes we
服务还可以，所以我们上传了吗
did Oh upload a black blob to primary
哦将黑色斑点上传到小学了吗
equals blah blah blah blah there's the
等于等等等等等等
URL go to the storage service thing here
URL转到此处的存储服务
and I can hit refresh
我可以刷新
I guess it's refresh and there it's
我想这很新鲜
gotta you it's not just cats a jpg it's
要你，它不只是猫jpg
cat - UUID jpg that's the one we just
猫-UUID jpg这就是我们刚刚得到的
uploaded and what do we think I'd double
上传了，我们认为我会加倍
click on that it says initializing open
点击它说初始化打开
of cat there we go there's our our blob
猫的我们去那里是我们的斑点
cat okay so there we go not bad huh we
猫好，所以我们走的还不错吧，我们
can actually very easily talk to the
实际上可以很容易地与
storage service that way and we can also
这样的存储服务，我们也可以
use the spring resource abstraction to
使用spring资源抽象来
read data from that as well the next
从中读取数据以及下一个
thing I wanna do is I wanna be able to
我想做的是我想
integrate my highly available cat
整合我的高可用猫
picture website I want to build in
我要建立的图片网站
support messaging across different nodes
支持跨不同节点的消息传递
from two different regions one way to do
来自两个不同区域的一种方法
that of course is to use azores service
那当然是使用亚速尔群岛服务
bus right and certain the service bus is
公交车的权利，并确定服务公交车是
fairly straightforward
非常坦率的
so you say you go to the build first of
所以你说你先去建
all and you bring in the right
所有，您带来了权利
dependency in this case the dependency
在这种情况下，依赖
matches the same sort of pattern as
匹配与
we've used elsewhere so uh let's see uh
我们在其他地方使用过，所以让我们看看
Xue er actually looks like this is
雪儿实际上看起来像这样
duplicated intelligence highlighting it
重复的情报突出了它
as though it's already been there so
好像它已经在那里
I'll just do that there we go so there's
我就那样做，我们去吧
the service bus in order for that to
服务总线，以便
work you need the configuration just
工作，您只需要配置
like before so service bus is a message
像以前一样，服务总线是一条消息
queue it's a message bus right and so
排队是一条消息总线，所以
you get the same you get them
你得到一样，你得到他们
information from the portal as we did
像我们一样从门户获取信息
before like this so service bus you
这样之前，这样服务巴士
click on that and you can see shared
单击该按钮，您可以看到共享的
access policies so remember you're gonna
访问策略，所以请记住您要
be you're gonna have producers and
是的，因为你要有制作人
consumers which may be different people
可能是不同人的消费者
may be doing groups they may not have
可能正在做他们可能没有的小组
access to the same permissions and their
访问相同的权限及其
view of the world is different the
世界观是不同的
producer will see the queue or the topic
生产者将看到队列或主题
to which they send messages the consumer
他们向其发送消息的消费者
will see a subscription that lives on
将会看到存在的订阅
the other end and it's connected to a
另一端，它连接到一个
cure topic but it is not a cure topic in
治愈主题，但不是治愈主题
this way it's a much more flexible API
这样，它是一个更加灵活的API
than JMS for example JMS is pretty
比JMS好，例如JMS
pretty naive right you have a you have a
很天真吧，你有一个，你有一个
single exchange a single destination for
一次交换一个目的地
both producer and consumer which means
生产者和消费者都意味着
that you want to change that you end up
你想要改变，最终
breaking one side of the other here I
我在这里打破另一侧
can add a little bit of indirection sort
可以添加一些间接排序
of like m2p
像m2p
right which by the way I don't think
对，顺便说一句，我不认为
it's particularly surprising given that
鉴于这特别令人惊讶
a lot of the mad scientists that a lot
很多疯狂的科学家
of mad science behind the Azur
Azur背后的疯狂科学
service bus was a led by a guy named
服务巴士是由一个叫
Clement masters who was a prolific and
克莱门特大师多产，
compete community genius there so click
在那里竞争社区天才，所以请单击
on queues these are point-to-point right
在队列中，这些都是点对点的
I've got no queues you can click on a
我没有队列，您可以点击
topic I've got one topic called messages
我有一个主题叫消息
topic and I'm gonna send a message and
主题，我要发送一条消息，
I've got one subscription to that
我有一个订阅
messages subscription and each
消息订阅和每个
subscription has a time to live it has a
订阅有时间，它有一个
lock duration etc so I can do all sorts
锁定持续时间等，因此我可以进行各种操作
of interesting things Eric and configure
有趣的事情Eric和配置
also to SLA or qlae information what I
也向SLA或qlae信息我
need to specify here is that I've got a
这里需要指定的是，我有一个
topic name called messages topic and
主题名称，称为消息主题和
I've got a subscription name called
我有一个名为
messages subscription here I'm
我在这里订阅消息
specifying what I want to do with the
指定我要使用的
data
数据
Pete o'clock means that I'm received
皮特的钟声表示我已收到
message is not delayed until somebody
消息不会延迟到有人
and so submit tell somebody process it
所以提交告诉别人处理它
right here it's received and
就在这里收到
automatically removed so we're just
自动删除，所以我们只是
assuming that you've you've done
假设你已经完成了
something with it right there's
正确的东西
something you've managed to work with it
您设法使用的东西
I'm gonna leave it in Pete o'clock and
我要把它留在皮特，
you should too I think unless you're
你也应该这样想，除非你是
sure and what we're gonna do is we write
当然，我们要做的就是写
a simple program that it's kind of silly
一个很傻的简单程序
but it you know it'll work we're gonna
但你知道它会起作用的
write a message that writes a message to
写一条消息，写一条消息到
the queue and then we consume it from
队列，然后我们从中使用它
the same component of the same
相同的组成部分
application
应用
okay log4j to private final topic client
可以将log4j转到私有最终主题客户端
private final I subscription client okay
私人最终I订阅客户端可以
there's that and event listener
有那个和事件监听器
application ready event okay and we're
应用就绪事件好了，我们
gonna just do a demo here that is going
只是在这里做一个演示
to register a listener a message
向收听者注册消息
subscriber first and then will consume
订户先消费，然后消费
the message so it's a it takes a few
消息，所以这是一个需要一些
seconds or a little bit of time for the
几秒钟或一点点的时间
registration to settle so we're going to
注册来解决，所以我们要
wait so I'm going to say this dot I
等待，所以我要说这个点
subscription client I register message
订阅客户端我注册消息
handler new and this will be a message
新的处理程序，这将是一条消息
header for let's see new message handler
标头，让我们看看新的消息处理程序
okay
好的
no good and we've got the injected
不好，我们已经注射了
mugger
抢劫犯
so it's logged out log that info
因此它已注销，记录该信息
received message
收到消息
let's save stock get body with message
让我们节省库存，让消息充满力量
ID or body ID message ID okay so there
ID或正文ID消息ID可以，所以
we go there's my message this is
我们去那里是我的信息，这是
actually a string I just got a byte
实际上是一个字符串，我只有一个字节
buffer I'm gonna turn that into a string
缓冲区我要把它变成一个字符串
here okay there's that and that's it now
好的，就是这样，就是这样
you could do some interesting things
你可以做一些有趣的事情
here you can handle the errors if they
如果他们在这里，您可以处理错误
hit should arise your code doesn't have
命中应该出现您的代码没有
any errors right there's no errors in
任何错误，就没有错误
your system but for others for the rest
您的系统，其余部分
of us this is a nice callback to have
对我们来说这是一个不错的回调
exception log that out very good okay so
异常日志，很好，所以
that's the subscription to the
这是对
registration now we want to use the
现在注册，我们要使用
topic client to send a message okay so a
主题客户端发送消息好吧
new message hello at instant dot now
即时点现在有新消息问好
adapt to string already and when I hit
当我击中时已经适应弦乐
Send and go got that configuration
发送并获得该配置
by the way em configuration 40 you've
顺便说一下，EM配置40
got shared access policies click on the
获取共享访问策略，请点击
one that you're using I'm using this one
您正在使用的一个我正在使用的一个
and that's where you get the keys and
那就是您获取钥匙的地方，
the primary connection is bringing all
主要的联系正在带来所有
that stuff that comes from the shared
来自共享的东西
access policy itself not from the topic
访问策略本身不是来自主题
or there or the queue that you may know
或那里或您可能知道的队列
that but that confused me for a minute
那让我困惑了一分钟
and a half I I will I'll just say that
我会说一半
right now books this might not work
现在预订这可能行不通
oh did it work receiving link I don't
哦，它能收到我的链接吗？
know if I registered I think I let me
知道我是否注册了，我想我让我了
see did that work we see message okay
看到这项工作了吗，我们看到消息了
good that did work I was able to get it
做得很好，我能够得到它
fast enough but usually or not music
足够快，但通常不是音乐
I suppose sometimes I have to do
我想有时候我必须做
something like this it and this is a
像这样的东西，这是一个
silly example right have to wait wait a
愚蠢的例子对吧，必须等一等
second and then send so you might you
第二，然后发送，这样你就可以了
know why am MV your mileage might bear
知道为什么您的里程可能是MV
I normally do that when I'm doing this
我通常在这样做的时候这样做
kind of a demo obviously you're very
一种演示，显然你非常
rarely gonna have a silly demo like
很少有像这样的愚蠢的演示
that's where you register to listen for
那是您注册收听的地方
messages that you yourself send yourself
您自己发送的邮件
what's the point of using message cubes
使用消息多维数据集有什么意义
or just talking to yourself but for two
或只是自言自语，只有两个
different nodes this won't be such a big
不同的节点，不会太大
deal like two different nodes across
像两个不同的节点一样处理
different instances and processes one
不同的实例和过程之一
okay all right so good we've got a whole
好吧，很好，我们有一个整体
bunch of stuff here we look to know that
一堆东​​西，我们希望知道
we're obviously you know we could take
我们显然是您知道我们可以接受
this application we should store all of
这个应用程序，我们应该存储所有
this configuration all this should be
这个配置应该是
lit you know I would never leave it in a
点燃你知道我永远不会把它放在一个
config file like this this is for a demo
像这样的配置文件是一个演示
you could use the ours or T vault to
您可以使用我们的或T库
store this information and in which case
存储此信息，在这种情况下
you would need a bootstrap configuration
您将需要一个引导程序配置
key that would then use that would in
然后将使用的密钥
turn be using an environment variable or
转向使用环境变量或
something like that you could deploy
可以部署的东西
this you can deploy this to the spring
这个你可以部署到春天
club config server which supports
支持的俱乐部配置服务器
symmetrically encrypted keys and values
对称加密的密钥和值
this you could use the knuckles from
这个你可以用
rally Bob but you can use that I mean
集会鲍勃，但你可以用我的意思
there's a whole bunch of places you
有很多地方你
could put this information definitely
可以肯定地把这些信息
not in your property file and certainly
不在您的财产文件中，当然
not gonna get right what do we do do not
不会正确，我们该怎么办
do not check this in to get that done I
不要签入以完成我
think we're ready to go to production
认为我们已经准备好投入生产
aren't we we've got an application it's
是不是我们有一个应用程序
it seems to work seems fine I should
似乎工作似乎很好，我应该
definitely run some tests of course but
当然可以运行一些测试，但是
but uh that's my first interesting does
但这是我的第一个有趣的事情
that love to go to production right now
那种爱现在就投入生产
but of course of course
但是当然
we're not really ready to go to
我们还没有准备好去
production are we not yet we are we
生产是我们还不是我们是我们
can't we have to account for
我们不必考虑
observability how observable how visible
可观察性如何可观察如何可见
is this application in production what
生产中的这个应用程序是什么
can we see about the behavior of the
我们可以看到有关
application in production and so what I
在生产中的应用等等
want to do is I want to plug in
想做的就是我要插入
Microsoft Azure insights application
Microsoft Azure见解应用程序
insights which isn't at the moment
目前尚无见解
managed by the spring boot bomb so it's
由弹簧靴炸弹管理，所以
actually a separate thing that has its
实际上是一个独立的东西
own dependency so I'm going to use the
自己的依赖关系，所以我将使用
azure application inside spring boots
弹簧靴内的天蓝色应用
starter and I'm gonna use one dot one oh
入门者，我要用一个点哦
babe
宝贝
okay and when I have that in the class
好的，当我上课的时候
pack the only thing I need left is the
打包我唯一需要剩下的就是
configuration of the name of them the
配置他们的名字
microservice spring application and
微服务春季应用和
that's just standard do you if you've
这是标准的吗？
ever used spring cloud you've had to do
曾经使用过的弹簧云
that before and the installation
之前和安装
instrumentation key okay and you can get
仪表键好了，您可以获得
that by going to application insights
通过深入了解应用程序
click on this and there's your
点击这个，那里是你的
instrumentation key separate place as
仪表键单独放置为
you know it's never in the it'd be nice
你知道它永远不会是美好的
if a bit like it'd be nice if every as
如果有点像，如果每个都很好
your service had just one screen that
您的服务只有一个屏幕
says configuration values that you need
说出您需要的配置值
to talk to this thing right here right
在这里谈论这个东西
but nope it's a little different in each
但不，每个都有点不同
one but otherwise really nice API so
一个但非常好的API，所以
here's the instrumentation key and with
这是仪表键，并带有
that I want to have a REST API wanna
我想拥有一个REST API
have something I can talk to just to
我有话要说
drive some traffic here so we'll say
在这里吸引一些流量，所以我们会说
class readings wrist wrist wrist wrist
班级读数腕腕腕
controller at get mapping hi string
控制器在获取映射嗨字符串
hello because my computer is so slow
你好，因为我的电脑太慢了
right now
马上
because I'm using Quicktime everything
因为我正在使用Quicktime的一切
my keystrokes are feeding back later
我的击键稍后反馈
than normal right so I'm typing things
比正常的权利，所以我在打字
I'm not seeing the errors it's not just
我没有看到错误，这不仅仅是
you it's actually me and the on the
你实际上是我，而在
producer side doesn't recording this
生产者方未记录此
feedback is slow ok so I've got my
反馈很慢，所以我有我的
little rest in point that's because I
一点休息就是因为我
want to be able to drive some traffic to
希望能够吸引一些流量
something something that we can then
一些我们可以做到的
measure and monitor and so
测量和监控等
that'll give us what we need it's just
那会给我们我们所需要的
hi okay so we start that
嗨，好吧，我们开始
already so that's up and running and we
已经开始运行了，我们
can actually make some traffic make some
实际上可以带来一些流量
requests curl HTTP localhost:8080
请求curl HTTP localhost：8080
for session hi is that work looks like
会话喜是工作看起来像
it works right so now let's just drive
它工作正常，所以现在让我们开车
some traffic with it while true do done
确实完成了一些流量
okay now we go to application insights
好的，现在我们来了解应用程序见解
click on bootiful Azur live metrics
单击可启动的Azur实时指标
stream five four three two one
流五四三二一
oh yeah
哦耶
so it's still connecting there we go you
所以它仍然在连接我们
can see some data going into the
可以看到一些数据进入了
application starting to take up there we
应用程序开始占用我们
go okay so as it does that I just
一切顺利，因为我只是
control ceded control see the request
控件让步控件请参见请求
[Music]
[音乐]
let's just see what happens
让我们看看发生了什么
there you go it's gonna flatline now
你去那里现在会变得平坦
right and you can see that teetering
对，你会看到摇摇欲坠
down in certain graphs so you get
在某些图表中向下，这样您就可以
automatic instrumentation of all this
所有这些的自动检测
good stuff you can see the analytics you
好东西，你可以看到你的分析
can see how many servers we got online
可以看到我们有多少台服务器在线
you can see request rate request
您可以看到请求率请求
duration also it's a very interesting
持续时间也很有趣
telemetry about the application all just
关于应用程序的遥测
by having the right key and the right
通过拥有正确的钥匙和正确的
starter all right my friends we have
首先，我的朋友们，我们有
looked at beautiful Microsoft Azure
看着美丽的微软Azure
we've looked at the incredible spring
我们看了令人难以置信的春天
boot and spring cloud integrations you
启动和Spring Cloud集成
can see that like all good spring
可以像所有的春天一样看到
integrations this one supports automatic
该集成支持自动
api's where appropriate and makes it
api在适当的地方并使其
easier to consume these things in a
更容易将这些东西消耗掉
cloud application you know you take
您知道需要的云应用程序
something like Microsoft Azure and Cloud
像Microsoft Azure和Cloud
Foundry to put them together you've got
代工将它们放在一起
yourself a winning combination that I
自己是我的成功组合
think is hard to beat
认为很难被击败
and you're done we've got a working
你完成了，我们已经在工作
thing that just works right so the
正确的事情，所以
platform manages all the infrastructure
平台管理所有基础架构
you can focus on the code that matters
您可以专注于重要的代码
and build world-class services that are
并建立世界一流的服务
built to last and built a scale
建立到最后并建立一个规模
worldwide in a global scale in a global
全球范围内
way so with that my friends thank you so
这样，我的朋友们就这样谢谢你
very much for watching and as always
非常适合观看，一如既往
we'll see you next
我们下次见
you
您